Guide to the Stanford University, Commission of Engineers, Records
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Photographs
  - Negatives of earthquake damage and reconstruction
    - Inner quad, staircase [Negative# 24-4 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, rear [Negative# 24-5 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, front [Negative# 24-6 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Building interior [Negative# 24-7 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Roof supports [?] [Negative# 24-8 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Memorial Arch after reconstruction [Negative# 24-9 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Interior supports [?] [Negative# 24-10 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Roof supports [Negative# 24-11], Undated (Box 8)
    - Quad, corner building [Negative# 24-12], Undated (Box 8)
    - Repairing arcades [Negative# 25-1 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Wall between Quad and engineering labs [Negative# 25-2 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Wall between Quad and engineering labs [Negative# 25-3 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Arcades, geology corner [Negative# 25-4 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Interior roof support damage [?] [Negative# 25-5 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Interior roof support damage [?] [Negative# 25-6 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Building interior [Negative# 25-7 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Interior wall damage [Negative# 25-8], Undated (Box 8)
    - Interior wall damage [Negative# 25-9 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Building interior [?] [Negative# 26-1 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, front [Negative# 26-2 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 26-3], Undated (Box 8)
    - Arcade [Negative# 26-4 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Arcade [Negative# 26-5 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Arcade [Negative# 26-6 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Arcade [Negative# 26-7 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Engineering lab [?] [Negative# 26-9], Undated (Box 8)
    - Quad corner [Negative# 26-10 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Quad building [Negative# 26-11], Undated (Box 8)
    - Arcade by rear of Church [Negative# 26-12], Undated (Box 8)
    - Arcade, read of Quad [Negative# 27-1 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Quad building [Negative# 27-2 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - View down Univ. Ave from Memorial Court [Negative# 27-3 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Rear of Quad buildings with staircase [Negative# 27-4 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Arcade on Quad corner [Negative# 27-5 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, rear [Negative# 27-6 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Front of Quad [Negative# 27-7], Undated (Box 8)
    - View down arcade [Negative# 27-8 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Front of Quad [Negative# 27-9], Undated (Box 8)
    - Quad building [Negative# 27-10 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Quad building [Negative# 27-12 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Quad corner building [Negative# 28-1 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 28-3], Undated (Box 9)
    - Rear of Quad [Negative# 28-4 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Rear of Quad [Negative# 28-5], Undated (Box 9)
    - Zoology building, front [Negative# 28-6 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 28-7 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Interior details [Negative# 28-8], Undated (Box 9)
    - Interior details [Negative# 28-9 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Arcade repair [Negative# 28-10 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Arcade repair [Negative# 28-11 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad corner building [Negative# 28-12 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad, corner building [Negative# 29-1 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 29-2 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 29-3 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Arcade repair [Negative# 29-4 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad, corner building [Negative# 29-5 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Zoology building [Negative# 29-6 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Chemistry building [Negative# 29-8 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Zoology building [Negative# 29-9 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Memorial Arch, reconstructed [Negative# 29-10 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Front of Quad (Memorial Arch) [Negative# 29-11 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Engineering labs [?] [Negative# 30-1 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Arcade repair [Negative# 30-2 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 30-3 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 30-4 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Arcade repair [Negative# 30-5 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Building stones [Negative# 30-6 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Engineering labs [?] [Negative# 30-7 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Arcade repair (rear of Quad) [Negative# 30-8 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 30-9 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Engineering labs [?] [Negative# 30-10 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Surface drainage ditch [Negative# 30-11 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 30-12 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 31-1], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad building and arcade [Negative# 31-2], Undated (Box 9)
    - Engineering labs [?] [Negative# 31-4 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Rear of Quad [Negative# 31-5], Undated (Box 9)
    - Rear of Quad [Negative# 31-6], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad building and arcade [Negative# 31-7 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 31-8 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 31-9 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Front of Quad, center entrance [Negative# 31-10 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Chemistry building [Negative# 31-11 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 31-12 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Engineering labs [?] [Negative# 32-1 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 32-2 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 32-3 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 32-4 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Rear of Quad [Negative# 32-5 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad building and arcade [Negative# 32-6 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 32-7 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 32-8 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Front of Quad, center entrance [Negative# 32-9 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 32-10 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 32-11 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad building and arcade [Negative# 32-12 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 33-1] (Box 9)
    - Geology corner [Negative# 33-2 ] (Box 9)
    - Geology corner [Negative# 33-3 ] (Box 9)
    - Close up of stone work [Negative# 33-4] (Box 9)
    - Close up of stone work [Negative# 33-5 ] (Box 9)
    - Creek or bridge repair [?] [Negative# 33-6 ] (Box 9)
    - Ditch [?] [Negative# 33-7 ] (Box 9)
    - Creek repair [?] [Negative# 33-10 ] (Box 9)
    - Creek or bridge repair [?] [Negative# 33-11 ] (Box 9)
    - Creek or bridge repair [?] [Negative# 33-12 ] (Box 9)
    - Drain pipe repair [?] [Negative# 34-1 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Drain pipe repair [?] [Negative# 34-2 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Creek and bridge repair [?] [Negative# 34-3], Undated (Box 9)
    - Drain pipe repair [?] [Negative# 34-3 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Creek and bridge repair [?] [Negative# 34-5 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Drain pipe repair [?] [Negative# 34-6 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Engineering labs [?] [Negative# 34-7 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Horses plowing [Negative# 34-8 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad, corner building [Negative# 34-9 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad, corner building [Negative# 34-10 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 34-11 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 34-12 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Ditch repair [?] [Negative# 35-1 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Ditch repair [?] [Negative# 35-2 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Creek [?] [Negative# 35-3 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Creek [?] [Negative# 35-4 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Creek or ditch repair [?] [Negative# 35-5 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad, corner building [Negative# 35-6 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad, corner building [Negative# 35-7 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Drain pipe [Negative# 35-8 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Drain pipe at rear of Quad [Negative# 35-9 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Arcade repair [Negative# 35-10 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 35-11 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad building and staircase [Negative# 35-12 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Ditch along side of Quad [Negative# 36-1 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Ditch by engineering labs [?] [Negative# 36-3 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Drain pipe and ditch, rear of Quad [Negative# 36-4 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Engineering labs [?] [Negative# 36-5 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad, corner building [Negative# 36-6 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Ditch [Negative# 36-7 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Ditch [Negative# 36-9 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Creek [?] [Negative# 36-10 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Ditch [Negative# 36-11 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Ditch [Negative# 36-12 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Creek [?] [Negative# 37-1 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Creek [?] [Negative# 37-3 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Ditch [Negative# 37-4 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Ditch [?] [Negative# 37-5 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Ditch and pipe by engineering labs [?] [Negative# 37-6 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Drain pip, side of Quad [Negative# 37-7 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 37-8 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 37-9 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Arcade repair [Negative# 37-10 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Arcade repair [Negative# 37-11 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Arcade (wall) detail [Negative# 37-12 ], Undated (Box 9)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 38-1 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 38-2 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 38-3 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Quad building [?] [Negative# 38-4 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 38-5 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 38-6 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 38-7 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 38-8 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Interior details [Negative# 38-10 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Quad, corner building [Negative# 38-12 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Drainage ditch [Negative# 39-5 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Creek or ditch repair [?] [Negative# 39-6 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Creek or ditch repair [?] [Negative# 39-7 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Ditch digging [Negative# 39-8 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Ditch digging [Negative# 39-9 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Ditch [Negative# 39-10 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Ditch along side of Quad [Negative# 39-11 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs [?] [Negative# 39-12 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Drainage ditch [Negative# 40-1 ], 1908 Jan (Box 10)
    - Ditch digging [Negative# 40-3 ], 1908 Jan (Box 10)
    - Ditch digging [Negative# 40-4 ], 1908 Jan (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs [?] [Negative# 40-5 ], 1908 Jan (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs [?] [Negative# 40-6 ], 1908 Jan (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs [?] [Negative# 40-7 ], 1908 Jan (Box 10)
    - Horses plowing [Negative# 40-8 ], 1908 Jan (Box 10)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 40-9 ], 1908 Jan (Box 10)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 40-10 ], 1908 Jan (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs [?] [Negative# 40-11 ], 1908 Jan (Box 10)
    - Wall detail [Negative# 40-12 ], 1908 Jan (Box 10)
    - Label with set 40 (Box 10)
    - Arcade repair [Negative# 41-1 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Building stone [Negative# 41-2 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Drainage ditch [Negative# 41-3 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Ditch or creek repair [?] [Negative# 41-4 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Ditch [Negative# 41-5 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Ditch [Negative# 41-6 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs [?] [Negative# 41-7 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs [?] [Negative# 41-8 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs [?] [Negative# 41-9 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs [?] [Negative# 41-10 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 41-11 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 41-12 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Wall detail [Negative# 42-1 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Wall detail [Negative# 42-2 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs [?] [Negative# 42-3 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs [?] [Negative# 42-4], Undated (Box 10)
    - Drainage ditch [Negative# 42-5 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Ditch work [Negative# 42-6 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Ditch work [?] [Negative# 42-7 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Ditch work [?] [Negative# 42-8 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Drainage ditch [Negative# 42-9 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Ditch [Negative# 42-10 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Lake Lagunita [?] [Negative# 42-12 ], Undated (Box 10)
    - Quad building, doorway [Negative# 43-1 ], 1908 Feb (Box 10)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 43-2 ], 1908 Feb (Box 10)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 43-3 ], 1908 Feb (Box 10)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 43-4 ], 1908 Feb (Box 10)
    - Quad building with staircase [Negative# 43-5 ], 1908 Feb (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs [?] [Negative# 43-6 ], 1908 Feb (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs [?] [Negative# 43-7 ], 1908 Feb (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs [?] [Negative# 43-8 ], 1908 Feb (Box 10)
    - Arcade repair [Negative# 43-9 ], 1908 Feb (Box 10)
    - Quad, corner building [Negative# 43-10 ], 1908 Feb (Box 10)
    - Quad, corner building [Negative# 43-11 ], 1908 Feb (Box 10)
    - Quad building [?] [Negative# 43-12 ], 1908 Feb (Box 10)
    - Label from set 43 (Box 10)
    - Wing 43-1 Quad corner building (Box 10)
    - Wing 43-2 Quad corner building (Box 10)
    - Wing 43-3 Construction detail (Box 10)
    - Wing 43-4 Quad corner building (Box 10)
    - Wing 43-5 Quad corner building (Box 10)
    - Wing 43-6 Engineering labs (Box 10)
    - Wing 43-7 Engineering labs (Box 10)
    - Wing 43-8 Engineering labs (Box 10)
    - Wing 43-9 Quad building (?) (Box 10)
    - Wing 43-10 Arcade repair (Box 10)
    - Wing 43-10 Roof support (Box 10)
    - Wing 43-12 Roof support (Box 10)
    - Wing unnumbered Front view of Quad, from oval (Box 10)
    - Wing unnumbered Front view of Quad, from oval (Box 10)
    - Envelope for Wing 43 set (Box 10)
    - Quad corner building [Negative# 45-1 ] (Box 10)
    - Quad corner building (rear) [Negative# 45-2] (Box 10)
    - Quad corner building (rear) [Negative# 45-3 ] (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 45-4 ] (Box 10)
    - Unidentified [Negative# 45-5] (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 45-6 ] (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 45-8 ] (Box 10)
    - Unidentified (near Post Office?) [Negative# 45-9 ] (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 45-10 ] (Box 10)
    - Quad portal [Negative# 45-12 ] (Box 10)
    - Quad arcade [Negative# 46-1 ] (Box 10)
    - Digging [Negative# 46-2 ] (Box 10)
    - Unidentified [Negative# 46-3 ] (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs (bldg. 02-530) [Negative# 46-5 ] (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 46-6 ] (Box 10)
    - Roof structure (engineering labs?) [Negative# 46-7 ] (Box 10)
    - Engineering labs (bldg. 02-530) [Negative# 46-8 ] (Box 10)
    - Quad arcade [Negative# 46-9] (Box 10)
    - Quad building with staircase (outside) [Negative# 46-10 ] (Box 10)
    - Quad portal [Negative# 46-11 ] (Box 10)
    - Quad arcade [Negative# 46-12 ] (Box 10)
    - Quad corner building (engineering?) [Negative# 47-1 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 47-2 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs (bldg. 02-530) [Negative# 47-3] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 47-4] (Box 11)
    - Unidentified (brick wall or fence) [Negative# 47-6 ] (Box 11)
    - Unidentified (brick wall or fence) [Negative# 47-7 ] (Box 11)
    - Unidentified (brick wall or fence) [Negative# 47-9 ] (Box 11)
    - Unidentified interior of building [Negative# 47-10 ] (Box 11)
    - Unidentified interior of building [Negative# 47-11] (Box 11)
    - Quad portal [Negative# 47-12 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad portal under construction [Negative# 48-1 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad portal under construction [Negative# 48-2 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad portal under construction [Negative# 48-3 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad portal under construction [Negative# 48-4 ] (Box 11)
    - Inner quad buildings [Negative# 48-5 ] (Box 11)
    - Construction, engineering buildings [Negative# 48-6 ] (Box 11)
    - Construction, engineering buildings [Negative# 48-7 ] (Box 11)
    - Horse-drawn cart in construction site (engineering?) [Negative# 48-8 ] (Box 11)
    - Construction, engineering buildings [Negative# 48-9 ] (Box 11)
    - Construction, structure unknown [Negative# 48-10 ] (Box 11)
    - Construction, structure unknown (same as 48-10) [Negative# 48-11 ] (Box 11)
    - Original envelope for 48-1 to 48-11 (Box 11)
    - Quad portal under construction [Negative# 49-1] (Box 11)
    - Quad portal under construction [Negative# 49-2] (Box 11)
    - Construction, engineering ? [Negative# 49-3 ] (Box 11)
    - Construction, engineering ? [Negative# 49-4 ] (Box 11)
    - Construction, engineering buildings [Negative# 49-5 ] (Box 11)
    - Construction, engineering buildings [Negative# 49-6 ] (Box 11)
    - Construction, engineering or foundry ? [Negative# 49-7 ] (Box 11)
    - Construction, structure unknown [Negative# 49-8 ] (Box 11)
    - Construction, engineering buildings [Negative# 49-9 ] (Box 11)
    - Construction, engineering buildings [Negative# 49-10] (Box 11)
    - Construction, engineering buildings [Negative# 49-11] (Box 11)
    - Construction, engineering buildings [Negative# 49-12 ] (Box 11)
    - Original envelope for 49-1 to 49-12 (Box 11)
    - Construction, engineering buildings [Negative# 50-1 ] (Box 11)
    - Construction, structure unknown [Negative# 50-2 ] (Box 11)
    - Wrought iron gate, close-up [Negative# 50-3 ] (Box 11)
    - Construction, inner quad building [Negative# 50-5 ] (Box 11)
    - Construction, inner quad building [Negative# 50-6 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad portals [Negative# 50-7 ] (Box 11)
    - Floor construction, engineering building? [Negative# 50-8 ] (Box 11)
    - Construction, engineering buildings [Negative# 50-9] (Box 11)
    - Construction, engineering buildings [Negative# 50-10 ] (Box 11)
    - Construction, engineering buildings [Negative# 50-11 ] (Box 11)
    - Construction, engineering buildings [Negative# 50-12 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 51-1 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 51-2 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 51-3 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 51-4 ] (Box 11)
    - Chemistry building [Negative# 51-5 ] (Box 11)
    - Old library (quad) [Negative# 51-6 ] (Box 11)
    - Residential area [Negative# 51-7 ] (Box 11)
    - Unidentified site [Negative# 51-8 ] (Box 11)
    - Unidentified site (by creek?) [Negative# 51-9 ] (Box 11)
    - Alley behind houses on campus [Negative# 51-10 ] (Box 11)
    - Unidentified site (dirt road, board fence) [Negative# 51-11 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad engineering corner and end of engineering labs [Negative# 51-12 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 52-1 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 52-2 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 52-3 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs (?) - interior [Negative# 52-4 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 52-5 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 52-8 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 52-9 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 52-10 ] (Box 11)
    - Unidentified interior [Negative# 52-11 ] (Box 11)
    - Close up of stone wall [Negative# 52-12 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 53-1] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 53-2 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 53-4 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad buildings (retiling roof) [Negative# 53-5 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 53-6 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 53-7 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 53-8 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 53-9 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 53-10 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 53-11 ] (Box 11)
    - Building interior [Negative# 54-1] (Box 11)
    - Close up of interior wall [Negative# 54-2 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 54-3 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 54-6 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 54-7 ] (Box 11)
    - Building interior showing trench in floor [Negative# 54-8 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 54-9] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 54-10 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 54-12] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 55-1 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs (building brick wall) [Negative# 55-2 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 55-3 ] (Box 11)
    - Unidentified wall [Negative# 55-4 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 55-5 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 55-6 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 55-7 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs (mounting mechanical device from rafters) [Negative# 55-8 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs interior [Negative# 55-9] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 55-10 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad buildings (?) [Negative# 55-11 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 55-12] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 56-1 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad - front view [Negative# 56-2 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad - front view [Negative# 56-3 ] (Box 11)
    - Arcade - arch repair [Negative# 56-4 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad building roof work (possibly bldg. 01-160) [Negative# 56-5 ] (Box 11)
    - Classroom interior under repair [Negative# 56-6 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 56-7 ] (Box 11)
    - Quad building roof work [Negative# 56-8] (Box 11)
    - Side of Quad [Negative# 56-9 ] (Box 11)
    - Lab interior [Negative# 56-10 ] (Box 11)
    - Classroom (or lab) interior [Negative# 56-11 ] (Box 11)
    - Engineering labs [Negative# 56-12 ] (Box 11)
  - Prints (cyanotypes and black/white) from numbered series
    - Mineralogy building [Negative# 4-2] (Box 12)
    - Business office arcade [Negative# 5-1] (Box 12)
    - Business office arcade [Negative# 5-2] (Box 12)
    - Gymnasium - wall of interior court [Negative# 12-11] (Box 12)
    - Arcade eng. building to business office [Negative# 13-4 ] (Box 12)
    - Physics building arcade at rear [Negative# 13-5 ] (Box 12)
    - Mechanical lab, s.w. corner [Negative# 14-1 ] (Box 12)
    - Boiler house, rear view [Negative# 14-2 ] (Box 12)
    - Woodworking shop, from s.w. [Negative# 14-3 ] (Box 12)
    - Blacksmith shop, north wall [Negative# 14-4 ] (Box 12)
    - Small physics building, c. arch to physics building [Negative# 14-5 ] (Box 12)
    - Encina Hall - west wing, west side [Negative# 14-6 ] (Box 12)
    - Encina Hall - west wing, east side [Negative# 14-7 ] (Box 12)
    - Encina Hall - east wing, west side [Negative# 14-8 ] (Box 12)
    - Arcades, law to admin. building (2 cc.) [Negative# 17-7 ] (Box 12)
    - Arcades, law to admin. building [Negative# 17-9 ] (Box 12)
    - Encina Hall - rear of west wing [Negative# 16-2 ] (Box 12)
    - Small c.e. building, s.w. corner [Negative# 18-1 ] (Box 12)
    - Arcades (ceiling), eng. building to business office [Negative# 18-2 ] (Box 12)
    - Engin. bldg. cross arch to business office [Negative# 18-3 ] (Box 12)
    - Arcade: engin. bldg. to business office, east wall [Negative# 18-4 ] (Box 12)
    - Arcade: engin. bldg. to business office, west wall [Negative# 18-5 ] (Box 12)
    - Hist & eng. building, s.w. walls (2 cc.) [Negative# 18-6] (Box 12)
    - Gymnasium, south side from library [Negative# 18-7 ] (Box 12)
    - Gymnasium, west side [Negative# 18-8 ] (Box 12)
    - Chemistry building, n.e. corner [Negative# 18-9 ] (Box 12)
    - Chemistry building, n.w. corner [Negative# 18-10 ] (Box 12)
    - Chemistry building, n.w. corner [Negative# 18-11 ] (Box 12)
    - Chemistry building, s.w. corner [Negative# 18-12 ] (Box 12)
    - Boiler house, front elevation [Negative# 19-1 ] (Box 12)
    - Mineralogy building, north avenue [Negative# 19-3 ] (Box 12)
    - Mineralogy building, north arcade [Negative# 19-4] (Box 12)
    - Arcades, physics bldg. to small physics bldg. [Negative# 19-5 ] (Box 12)
    - Physics bldg. cross arch to small physics bldg. (2 cc.) [Negative# 19-6 ] (Box 12)
    - Arcade, physics bldg. to small physics bldg. [Negative# 19-7 ] (Box 12)
    - Arcade, physics bldg. to small physics bldg. (2 cc.) [Negative# 19-8 ] (Box 12)